armedforcesloans.com 2007-10-11

# Welcome to Armed Forces Military Loans

**PRIVACY POLICY**    
  
**At Armed  Forces Loans of Nevada Inc. (AFL), respecting the ****_privacy_**** and ****_security_**** of your personal information is important to us. We encourage you to read this policy carefully and call us to discuss it if you have any questions. We want to make sure that your personal information is protected, and that you understand the policies that protect you. You'll find the same terms used in many companies' privacy policies.   **     

**We may share all the information that we collect, as described above, for the following purposes:**

> *** To provide you with the products and services you requested.**
> 
> *** To offer you additional products and services, from us or from others, that may be of interest to you.**
> 
> *** To comply with reporting and other legal requirements.**
> 
> *** To otherwise conduct business.**

**Information Sharing Among Our Family of Affiliated Companies:**

**Any company that is owned or controlled by  AFL list affiliates, its affiliated companies, and the other companies owned by AFL may receive information that we have obtained from you. That information is referred to in this Privacy Policy as "transaction information."You have the right to ensure that other information is not shared with our affiliates. If you don't want us to share this information please send us the request in writing to opt out. Once we receive your opt out request, we will stop sharing this information as soon as reasonably practical. our opt out will apply to all accounts you hold individually and to all accounts you hold jointly with other persons. Your opt out will not apply, however, to any accounts your joint account holders hold individually or jointly with personal other than you. In your joint account holders wish to opt out as to such other accounts, they will need to submit a separate opt out request.**

**Information Sharing with Nonaffiliated Third Parties as Permitted by Law:**

**We are permitted by law to share all the information we collect, as described above, with (1) companies that perform marketing services on our behalf and (2) with other institutions with whom we have joint marketing arrangements. For example, we may share all the information we collect, as described above, with other nonaffiliated third parties that assist us with preparing monthly statements and with the processing and printing of checks. Please be advised that the opt out rights described below will not apply to the sharing of information with these third parties or to the sharing of information with marketing service providers and joint marketers as described above.**

**Information Sharing with Other Nonaffiliated Third Parties and Your Opt Out Rights:**

**Unless you request otherwise, we may share all the information we collect, as described above, with additional types of nonaffiliated third parties, such as:**

> *** Financial service providers, such as life insurance companies for whom one or more of our affiliates acts as agents.**
> 
> *** Nonaffiliated companies, such as firms that offer value-added packages of products and services including discounted travel services, credit councelling, credit repair, debt management, discounted hotel accommodations and shopping services.**

**If you prefer that we not share your nonpublic personal information with these nonaffiliated third parties, you may opt out of those disclosures (other than those permitted by law) by sending us the request in writing. We will stop sharing this information as soon as reasonably practical. Again, your opt out will apply to all accounts you hold individually and to all accounts you hold jointly with other persons. Your opt out will not apply, however, to any accounts your going account holder held individually or jointly with persons other than you. If your joint account holders wish to opt out as to such other accounts, they will need to submit a separate opt out request.**

******FAX :       ** **702 868 6246****    OR    1-800-698-0914  
PHONE :  ****702 868 6204****    OR    **1-800-706-9676  
**EMAIL Questions:    [admin@armedforcesloans.com](mailto:admin@armedforcesloans.com) ******

**Home** **|** **About Us** **|**[ **Application**](https://www.armedforcesloans.com/application.asp) **|** **Questions** **|** **Privacy**
